// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "When was the Power Land established?",
    answer: "2021",
    options: [
      "2019",
      "2020",
      "2021",
      "2009"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who was the president during Power Land's establishment?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Onifade Abigail",
      "Bola Ahmed Tinubu",
      "Elusoji Feyikemi",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who took prayer session on CACCF Drama Night?",
    answer: "Bro Blessing",
    options: [
      "Sis Lolade",
      "Bro Blessing",
      "Bro Joshua",
      "Sis Abigail"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What's the Greek word for prayer?",
    answer: "Proseuche",
    options: [
      "Lambano",
      "Alhamdulillah",
      "Prayoques",
      "Proseuche"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of these men prayed while his face was between his knees ?",
    answer: "Elijah",
    options: [
      "Elisha",
      "Jesus",
      "Onewo Theophilus",
      "Elijah"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What time does prayer meeting start on Monday?",
    answer: "17:00",
    options: [
      "5:30pm",
      "17:00",
      "5:15pm",
      "16:00"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What's the prayer unit's tenure theme?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Rekindling",
      "Rekindling the fire of dead pulpit",
      "Renewing the fire on dead altars",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The Greek word for Bible is?",
    answer: "Biblos",
    options: [
      "Biblos",
      "Bibliah",
      "Biblios",
      "Biblah"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The Hebrew word 'Chaya' means ___",
    answer: "To be quickened",
    options: [
      "Refinary",
      "To be quickened",
      "To grow",
      "To love"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the name of Moses' two sons?",
    answer: "Gershom and Eliezer",
    options: [
      "Eliezer and Elipaz",
      "Elihu and Shemim",
      "Gershom and Eliezer",
      "Gershun and Eleazar"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of these scripture pertains to prayer?",
    answer: "Psalm 66:19",
    options: [
      "Psalm 66:19",
      "Luke 19:1",
      "John 6:2",
      "Revelations 1:8"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 12,
    question: "Who made the statement 'asiri ori pepe o kin tu'?",
    answer: "Bro Joshua",
    options: [
      "Bro Blessing",
      "Pastor Samuel",
      "Bro Joshua",
      "Sam Ogidiolu"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "What's the name of the present Prayer Cord?",
    answer: "Oyedamola",
    options: [
      "Oyetem",
      "Oyedamole",
      "Oyedamope",
      "Oyedamola"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 14,
    question: "God speaks to whom by the river Cheba?",
    answer: "Ezekiel",
    options: [
      "Ezekiel",
      "Isaiah",
      "Moses",
      "Joshua"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 15,
    question: "In 1Corinthians 16: Anathema means ",
    answer: "Accursed",
    options: [
      "Abuse",
      "Accursed",
      "Go thee behind Satan",
      "God my strength"
    ]
  },

];